ABAH DIVINE ELIKPLIM

GRAPHIC/UI/UX DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

CONTACT



+233-201-955-961



(divine.e.abah@gmail.com





www.deeveli.com

PROFILE

I enjoy designing and building vibrant platforms for our modern age. In the space of software design and development, I have with 4+ years crafting user-centric experiences across web, app, and soon, AR.

Also, I have good experience in marketing and sales and I am seeking to join a team that pushes boundaries and shapes the future, pixel by pixel, user by user while enjoying every bit of it.

SKILL

Design & Media: Graphic, UI/UX, Video Editing

Productivity: MS Suite, DevOps, GitHub, Vercel. Al Tools

Commitment: Leadership, People Relations, Proactive-problem Solving, Negotiation, Communications

Development: Mobile/Web App Front-end Development, WordPress

Marketing & Sales: Social Media Marketing, Strategy & Content, Customer Acquisition, Copywriting, Market Research

EXPERIENCE

၃ Creatives and Mobile Applications Developer

Axxend Corporation, Accra, Ghana

09/2023 - 01/2024

Microsoft Gold Partner company specialized in licensing and custom business solutions.

- Created wireframes, prototypes, and high-fidelity mockups using design tools, Figma and Adobe XD, adhering to design principles and brand guidelines.
- Integrated back-end APIs and services to build dynamic display and interactive user interfaces.
- Developed reusable UI components to improve development efficiency and code maintainability.
- Translated designs into clean, efficient, and maintainable code using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript frameworks like React or NextJs.
- Optimized performance by code refactoring, caching strategies, and image optimization techniques.

Contact: Mr. Elijah Awini,

Head of Technology and Innovation, +233501394289

ABAH DIVINE ELIKPLIM

UI/UX DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

Creatives Associate

Pearson Consultancy, Accra, Ghana

10/2022 - 08/2023

A startup marketing firm specialized in online and offline marketing.

- Designed and implemented user-friendly interfaces for client websites and mobile apps, resulting in a significant increase in customer engagement.
- Created high-quality visuals for presentations, social media posts, and marketing materials, contributing to a consistent brand identity.
- Supported the development of marketing collateral, including brochures, presentations, and infographics.
- Designed internal branding materials, including employee handbooks and onboarding presentations.
- Created marketing strategies and assisted in developing marketing campaigns.
- Aided in scriptwriting and storyboarding for video projects, contributing to clear and engaging narratives.

Contact: Mrs. Priscilla Boateng,

Marketing Lead, +233274234667

Creatives Associate, NSS

Axxend Corporation, Accra, Ghana

10/2021 – 08/2022

Microsoft Gold Partner company specialized in licensing and custom business solutions.

- Prototyped and tested innovative mobile app features to enhance user experience.
- Increased user engagement through intuitive and visually appealing website redesign.
- Created visually appealing marketing materials for print and digital campaigns.

Contact: Mr. Justice Kwarteng,

Head of Training, +233202510856

ABAH DIVINE ELIKPLIM

UI/UX DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

EDUCATION

 BSc. Computer Engineering Ghana Technology University College 2017-2021 General Science
 Action Senior High Technical School 2014-2016

CERTIFICATES

- 2nd Class Upper, BSc. Computer Engineering, Ghana Communication Technology University(KNUST affiliated)
- WASSCE, West African Secondary Schools Certificate Examination 2016

- Accenture User Experience Design 2020
- Aleph Global Digital Marketer 2023

STACKS

 NextJS, React, HTML, CSS(Tailwind, ShadCN, MUI, Headless UI)

INTEREST

Code, Design, Robotics, AR, VR & MR,
 Futuristic Tech, Research, DIYs, Hardware Fixes